J. Peter Lesley Papers 1826-1898 Mss.B.L56
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. General correspondence, 1826-1898 (Box 1)
  - to Ambrose E. Lehman, 1881 Sept. 23; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 21)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1881 Sept. 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 21)
  - John J. Black to J. P. Lesley, 1881 Sept. 26 (Box 21)
  - Concerning Ames' work, 1881 Oct. 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 21)
  - to Alfred R. Selwyn, 1881 Oct. 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 21)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1881 Oct. 14; Barois, Charles (Box 21)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1881 Oct. 21; Fontaine, William M. (Box 21)
  - Samuel Hill to J. P. Lesley, 1881 Nov. 1 (Box 21)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1881 Nov. 14; Hall, James (Box 21)
  - to Mr. Ingham, 1881 Nov. 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 21)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1881 Nov. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 21)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1881 Nov. 24; Davis, William M. (Box 21)
  - to Prof. Claypole, 1881 Nov. 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 21)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1881 Dec. 1; Hall, James (Box 21)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1881 Dec. 7; Barois, Charles (Box 21)
  - James Geikie to J. P. Lesley, 1881 Dec. 21 (Box 21)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Jan. 3; Desor, Edouard (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Jan. 11; Desor, Edouard (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Jan. 17; Spencer, J. W. (Box 22)
  - James Geikie to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Jan. 30 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Feb. 18; Desor, Edouard (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Feb. 22; Barois, Charles (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 March 23; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 April 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to James D. Dana, 1882 April 23; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 April 26; Desor, Edouard (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 May 2; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. C. White, 1882 May 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to James Hall, 1882 May 11; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 May 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 May 22; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to Thomas M. Bayne, 1882 May 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 June 2; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 June 3; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - Leo Lesquerex to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 June 4 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 June 22; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 June 25; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to Stevenson, 1882 July 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 July 25; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to C. A. Ashburner, 1882 Aug. 4; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to Stevenson, 1882 Aug. 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1882 Sept. 3; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Sept. 11; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Sept. 19; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1882 Sept. 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Oct. 1; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - Notcie of the death fo Mrs. Sophie Henrietts Lesquereux, wife of L. Lesquereux, 1882 Oct. 3 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Oct. 24; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Oct. 28; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to James Hall, 1882 Oct. 31; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Nov. 2; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Nov. 11; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to D. Appleton and Co., 1882 Nov. 13; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to White, 1882 Dec. 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Dec. 8; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to E. W. Claypole, 1882 Dec. 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to D. H. Mason, 1882 Dec. 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to Stevenson, 1882 Dec. 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Dec. 10; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1882 Dec. 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1882 Dec. 31; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Jan. 11; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Jan. 11; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1883 Jan. 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Jan. 17; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Jan. 23; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to E. M. McConnell, 1883 Jan. 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to F. A. P. B arnard, 1883 Feb. 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Feb. 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Feb. 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 March 12; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 March 26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1883 March 30; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. D. Dana, 1883 April 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Hare and Co. and Mitchell, 1883 May 23; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 May 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 June 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 July 11; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 22)
  - to C. W. Townsend, 1883 June 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1883 June 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 June? 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 July 7; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 July 8; Barois, Charles (Box 22)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1883 July 12; Haupt, Lewis M., (Lewis Muhlenberg), b. 1844 (Box 22)
  - F. E. Adams to J. P. Lesley, 1883 July 17 (Box 22)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1883 July 17; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 July 18; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to Major Powell, 1883 July 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 July 20; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Aug. 1; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Aug. 10; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Sept. 3; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to E. W. Claypole, 1883 Sept. 10; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Sept. 15; Hall, James (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Sept. 25; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Sept. 29; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Oct. 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - Sarah M. Hall to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Oct. 26 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Nov. 10; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. W. Powell, 1883 Dec. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. W. Powell, 1883 Dec. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. W. Powell?, 1883 Dec. 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Dec. 25; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 22)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1883 Dec. 28; Barois, Charles (Box 22)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1883 Dec. 30; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to C. E. Hitchcock, 1883 Dec. 31; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 22)
  - to James Hall, 1884 Jan. 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Jan. 13; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Jan. 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Jan. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Jan. 26; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Jan. 26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Feb. 6; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to Jones, Simpson, and Company, 1884 Feb. 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Feb. 19; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to H. C. Lewis, 1884 March 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 March 3; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 March 7; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to J. W. Powell, 1884 March 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 March 10; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to Dr. Newberry, 1884 March 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 March 17; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science. Invitation to the annual meeting... form letter, 1884 March 24 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 March 24; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to Prof. Claypole, 1884 March 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 March 29; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 April 1; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 April 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 April 20; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 April 23; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1884 May 2; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 May 3; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 May 19; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - William Forley to J. P. Lesley, 1884 May 20 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 May 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - Charles Scriber's Sons to J. P. Lesley, 1884 May 26 (Box 23)
  - to Samuel J. Randall, 1884 May 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 May 28; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to "My dear James Hall", 1884 May 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 June 2; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 June 2; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - Edgar Northington to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 June 28 (Box 23)
  - William Benjamin Carpenter to Prof. Peter Lesley, 1884 July 3 (Box 23)
  - John S. Black to J. P. Lesley, 1884 July 10 (Box 23)
  - E. L. Youmans to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 July 16 (Box 23)
  - E. L. Youmans to E. B. Harden, 1884 July 30 (Box 23)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1884 Aug. 4; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - Abstract or summary of letter to Jesse G. Burke, 1884 Aug. 22; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Aug. 22; Hall, James (Box 23)
  - J. Welland Reade to J. P. Lesley, 1884 Sept. 1 (Box 23)
  - to Prof. Claypole, 1884 Sept. 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Sept. 29; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - Mrs. John Bost Announcement of daughter's marriage, 1884 Oct. 2 (Box 23)
  - Mme. Charon-Morin Announcement of son's marriage, 1884 Oct. 2 (Box 23)
  - to J. W. Powell, 1884 Oct. 22; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. E. Hilgard, 1884 Oct. 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1884 Oct. 31; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - Anne Hampton Brewster to Prof. Peter Lesley, 1884 Nov. 15 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Nov. 19; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - John Murray Forbes to Prof. Peter Lesley, 1884 Nov. 20 (Box 23)
  - to Robert E. Pattison, 1884 Nov. 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to W. M. Quiggle, 1884 Nov. 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Nov. 29; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - Announcement by Charles Barrois of the birth of a son..., 1884 Nov. 30 (Box 23)
  - Edward Orton to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Dec. 3 (Box 23)
  - Mrs. Caroline L. Broomall to Prof. J. P. Lesley, 1884 Dec. 15 (Box 23)
  - to Hugh McCulloch, 1884 Dec. 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1884 Dec. 30; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - Robert E. Pattison to Hugh McCulloch, 1884 Dec. (Box 23)
  - to Jerome B. Niles, 1885 Jan. 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - Geological society of London to J. P. Lesley signed by T. G. Bonney, president, 1885 Jan. 30 (Box 23)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1885 Feb. 10; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1885 Feb. 17; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to Benjamin Herr, 1885 Feb. 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1885 Feb. 24; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to J. W. Powell, 1885 Feb. 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. W. Powell, 1885 Feb. 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1885 March 3; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to Mr. Scott, 1885 March 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - L. R. Warrington to J. P. Lesley, 1885 March 6 (Box 23)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1885 March 11; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1885 March 12; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1885 April 6; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1885 April 6; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to the Hon. Woodward, 1885 April 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to John P. S. Tobin, 1885 April 13; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to O. C. Marsh, 1885 April 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - Jinzoo Adachi to J. P. Lesley, 1885 April 29 (Box 23)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1885 May 6; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to Mr. McCormick, 1885 May 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1885 May 28; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - Dane S. Hart to J. P. Lesley, 1885 June 18 (Box 23)
  - to J. W. Powell, 1885 July 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to S. Q. Brown, 1885 July 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1885 July 17; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1885 Aug. 22; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - The geology of natural gas..., 1885 Aug. 24; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1885 Sept. 5; Ashburner, Charles A. (Box 23)
  - B. F. McDaniel to Peter Lesley, 1885 Sept. 7 (Box 23)
  - Alonzo Linn to J. P. Lesley, 1885 Sept. 8 (Box 23)
  - Charles E. Quitil to Charles A. Ashburner, 1885 Sept. 8 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1885 Sept. 16; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - Thomas J. Edge to J. P. Lesley, 1885 Sept. 22 (Box 23)
  - E. B. Harden to Thomas J. Edge, 1885 Oct. 8 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1885 Nov. 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - Frederick Fraley to J. P. Lesley, 1885 Nov. 7 (Box 23)
  - to James R. Mafarlane, 1885 Nov. 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to Dr. Orton, 1885 Dec. 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1885 Dec. 3; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1885 Dec. 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1885 Dec. 10; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1885 Dec. 22; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1885 Dec. 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 23)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1885 Dec. 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to William Pepper, 1885 Dec. 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 23)
  - to Charles Barrois, 1886 Jan. 4; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to Titns S. Emery, 1886 Jan. 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to Jesse Y. Burk, 1886 Jan. 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to B. S. Lyman, 1886 Jan. 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 Jan. 13; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Joseph Lesley, 1886 Jan. 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1886 Jan. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 Jan. 25; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 Jan. 30; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1886 Jan. 31; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to N. G. Parke, 1886 Feb. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 Feb. 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1886 Feb. 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1886 Feb. 11; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to L. Clark Seelye, 1886 Feb. 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 March 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1886 March 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to Mr. Wild, 1886 March 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1886 March 11; Hall, James (Box 24)
  - to J. A. Price, 1886 March 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 March 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1886 March 23; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. W. Powell, 1886 March 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to Mr. Shaffer, 1886 March 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 March 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 April 3; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1886 April 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 April 6; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1886 April 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 April 10; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 April 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to John Phelps Taylor, 1886 April 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux?, 1886 April 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley on the Crimora mine, 1886 April 22; Fulton, John (Box 24)
  - Leo Lesquere x to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 April 26 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1886 April 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1886 May 8; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1886 May 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 May 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1886 May 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. W. Powell, 1886 June 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 June 3; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1886 June 11; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 July 10; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 July 10; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1886 July 19; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 Aug. 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 Sept. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1886 Oct. 30; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to M. em de Margerie, 1886 Nov. 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1886 Nov i.e. Oct.26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1886 Dec. 20; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1886 Dec. 29; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 24)
  - Concerning the state geological survey, 1886?; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - Material pertaining to the cost of publishing the reports of the Second Geological Survey of Penna..., 1886; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - Material pertaining to plates for the reports of the Second Geological Survey of Penna..., 1886?; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - Material pertaining to iron ore for the Second Geological Survey of Penna..., 1886?; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - Material pertaining to manganese ores for the Second Geological Survey of Penna..., 1886?; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - Material pertaining to gold for the Second Geological Survey of Penna..., 1886?; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 24)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1887 Jan. 13; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1887 Feb. 8; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1887 March 19; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1887 March 26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1887 June 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to James? Hall, 1887 Aug. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1887 Aug. 25; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1887 Sept. 26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1887 Oct. 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1887 Dec. 25; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to James Hall, 1888 Feb. 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to Emmanuel de Margarie, 1888 Feb. 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to William A. Earkman, 1888 March 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1888 April 29; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to E. K. Meyers, 1888 Aug. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - Ford and Green to J. Peter Lesley, 1888 Aug. 18 (Box 25)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1888 Sept. 20; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1888 Sept. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1888 Sept. 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1888 Oct. 31; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to Mr. Dana, 1888 Dec. 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - Thomas Dinclair and Son to Leo Lesquereux, 1888 Dec. 28 (Box 25)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1888 Dec. 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1889 Jan. 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1889 Jan. 3; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1889 Jan. 5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1889 Jan. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 25)
  - to J. C. White, 1889 March 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1889 March 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to Mr. Dana, 1889 April 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
    see 1882 April 14
  - to F. W. Putnam, 1889 May 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to Charles A. Miner, 1889 June 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to Mr. Sheafer, 1889 Oct. 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to Hugh Hamilton, 1889 Oct. 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 25)
  - to Eugene A. Smith, 1890 Jan. 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)
  - to J. W. Dawson, 1890 Jan. 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)
  - to Mr. Newberry, 1890 March 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)
  - to "My Dear Ruth", 1890 March 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)
  - The preparation of Greece for the preaching of Paul, 1891 March 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)
    General note
    OMIT OMIT OMIT
  - to Mrs. Ashburner, 1890 April 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)
  - to Peter Sheafer, 1890 June 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)
  - to Adam Koone, 1890 Oct. 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)
  - to James Hall, 1890 Dec. 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)
  - to Mr. Walcott, 1891 Jan. 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)
  - to Mr. Walcott, 1891 Feb. 22; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 26)